<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogs>

    
    <dialog concept="goals" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="what are your goals for using EDM?" poke_message="How do you think you might be able to use EDM in your career going forward?">
    	
        <intro>
As the class is wrapping up this week, I thought it might be nice to discuss some of what you’ve learned the last few weeks. Let’s start with your goals for using EDM. How do you think you might be able to use EDM in your career going forward?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
    <dialog concept="which algorithms or methods" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="which algorithms or methods might be useful for your goals?" poke_message="Which algorithms or methods do you think might be useful to those goals?">
    	
        <intro>
Those are some important problems all right. (And if they weren’t, well, I’m just an automated agent without natural language processing or text mining capabilities). Which algorithms or methods do you think might be useful to those goals?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
    <dialog concept="things to keep in mind" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="what should you keep in mind when using those algorithms?" poke_message="When you use those algorithms or methods, what do you want to try to keep in mind?">
    	
        <intro>
When you use those algorithms or methods, what do you need to keep in mind? Are there any important considerations you’re going to be sure to take into account? Could be anything. What have you learned through this class that will influence *how* you use those algorithms?
        </intro>
    </dialog>
    <dialog concept="what surprised you" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="what surprised you?" poke_message="What from this class (that you learned about EDM) surprised you?">
    	
        <intro>
Moving more broadly, what from this class (that you learned about EDM) surprised you?  (Stay focused on EDM please; don’t talk about my human equivalent’s speed of talking…)
        </intro>
    </dialog>  
                          
    <dialog concept="FINISH" scenario="scenario-donothing.xml" description="">
    	
        <intro>
All right! You’re all done with the last Bazaar activity! Thanks for being part of the class. I hope you enjoyed it and found it interesting. Please leave feedback and comments on the discussion forum as you go. And please stay in touch! For the last time (this class), I’m Virtual Ryan Baker, and this has been Big Data and Education. I will now continue the chat activity again starting from the first prompt for anyone who missed the initial prompts.
        </intro>
    </dialog>   
</dialogs>
